{
    "subject": "resource/Louis,_Duke_of_Burgundy",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/France",
    "human_readable": "Louis, Duke of Burgundy was born in France.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9851897358894348,
            "question": "Was Louis, Duke of Burgundy born in a specific region of France?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9800103306770325,
            "question": "What was the significance of Louis, Duke of Burgundy's birth in France?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9449267387390137,
            "question": "Where was Louis, Duke of Burgundy born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6290703415870667,
            "question": "Who were some notable people that Louis, Duke of Burgundy interacted with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5838274359703064,
            "question": "What historical period did Louis, Duke of Burgundy live in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5735160112380981,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Louis, Duke of Burgundy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4362296164035797,
            "question": "What events shaped Louis, Duke of Burgundy's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42248037457466125,
            "question": "Did Louis, Duke of Burgundy have any significant accomplishments?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36169567704200745,
            "question": "Are there any historical records or documents related to Louis, Duke of Burgundy's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09728308022022247,
            "question": "What title did Louis hold?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Louis, Duke of Burgundy was born in France.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3616_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any historical records or documents related to Louis, Duke of Burgundy's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3616_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Louis, Duke of Burgundy have any significant accomplishments?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3616_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What events shaped Louis, Duke of Burgundy's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3616_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3616_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3616_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3616_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3616_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3616_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3616_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3616_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3616_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3616_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3616_78.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the requested format:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThis is because all four documents mention that Louis, Duke of Burgundy, was indeed born in France. Specifically, document #1 mentions that he was \"born at the Palace of Versailles in France\", and documents #5, #7, #8, and #9 also mention his birthplace as France or specifically the Palace of Versailles in France."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that Louis, Duke of Burgundy was indeed born in the Palace of Versailles in France on August 16, 1682. Therefore, the statement \"Louis, Duke of Burgundy was born in France\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}